Please, Prophet T.B. Joshua, revive my husband!
Please, Prophet T.B. Joshua, revive my husband. He is using a wheelchair.
My husband cannot breathe without this.
He cannot walk. He cannot breathe.
Please help!
He is using a wheelchair and he cannot breathe.
Healing In Jesus' Name
We are just coming from the hospital.
Please help me! Save me!
We came in an ambulance.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Thank You, Jesus!
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord!
The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed In Jesus' Name
Let him walk to the edge over there.
The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You!
Thank You, Jesus, for reviving me!
The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
SOUTH KOREA CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA
Testimony continues
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Kim Jae Sik - 69 years old
Kim Jae Sik - Seoul, South Korea
My name is Kim Jae Sik. I am 69 years old.
I am from Seoul, South Korea.
Who is the woman next to you?
She is my wife.
I came to meet Prophet T.B. Joshua because I had heart pain.
I came to this Crusade because of my heart and respiratory problem.
For how long did you have this problem?
I suffered from this problem for 20 years.
I couldn't do anything; so, my wife suffered because she always had to work hard.
If I didn't use the breathing machine, I could not breathe.
After Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I removed the oxygen mask.
Now, I can move freely.
I couldn't breathe on my own. I had to use a respirator and oxygen bottle to breathe.
After the prayer, I disconnected it.
I went to many hospitals.
I went to prayer mountains.
I went to many different places in search of a solution.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I removed the oxygen machine
and now I can breathe freely.
Before, I used to visit several hospitals and also prayer mountains.
But the solution was only in the Crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Why were you using an oxygen machine?
I couldn't breathe, so I had to use the oxygen machine to breathe.
What happened when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you?
My heart became light and I felt like running. So, I did.
I felt very fresh in my heart and suddenly I felt that I could walk and run now.
After removing the breathing machine, I can now move around, breathe, talk and walk freely.
I feel now very good because before, I used to use an oxygen machine
but that was very uncomfortable.
But now I don't use this so I can freely live my daily life.
What are the things you can do now to confirm that you are healed?
Before, I couldn't walk properly but now, I can walk freely and I am fine.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Yes, now I can run and do push ups.
Mr. Kim jumps up to the glory of God and demonstrates how he can now move freely,
and even do push ups pain-free.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Before, I was not able to do these things but now, I am very able to do this.
I can breathe freely after Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me.
So, I can testify that you too will be healed if Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for you, in Jesus' name.
I want to tell you that I am healed by God who worked through Prophet T.B. Joshua.
So, I want to tell you that you will also be healed if you get prayed for by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God is working through him, in Jesus' name.
Jeong Jin Hui - Seoul, South Korea
My name is Jeong Jin Hui. I am 53 years old.
I am from Seoul, South Korea.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
He is my husband.
He had a heart problem and had an operation.
He was in the hospital and couldn't breathe without a breathing machine.
This was why we came to the Crusade.
My husband had a heart surgery,
and he couldn't breathe well without a respirator and oxygen bottles.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I felt bad seeing him not able to breathe.
I felt very sad to just look at him being sick and having a problem with his heart.
How do you feel after Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for your husband?
I am very happy.
How do you feel when you see your husband breathing without any devices - respirator and oxygen bottle?
Thank You, Jesus. I want my husband to stay healthy and spread the Gospel.
I am very thankful to Jesus Christ, and I want my husband to live for spreading the Gospel.
Hallelujah! Thank You, Jesus! Thank You for healing my husband.
I really want everyone to encounter Jesus Christ.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Climbing up the winding staircase, it is difficult to believe
that Mr. Kim was once confined to a wheelchair
and unable to breathe without an oxygen machine.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
A group of visitors from Singapore who attended the crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua
recognise Mr. Kim and rejoice with him,
giving thanks to God for his miraculous healing.
They share their experience as they remember the deplorable condition
in which Mr. Kim came to the crusade.
I am Mathew Ng from Singapore.
I am now meeting this gentleman who we first met during the crusade.
When we met him, he was very ill and we remember seeing him with tubes
all over his hands and body.
He was in a wheelchair and even used an oxygen tank.
Now, we are looking at him totally restored and healed
by the mighty power of the Lord, Jesus Christ, through Prophet T.B. Joshua of The SCOAN.
I'm just so happy!
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2